Loot Hello friends, Namaskar, welcome to all of you once
again in our today's video,
friends, in today's video we will talk about
if you have taken an insurance from SBI and if
you have
sold your cars, bikes or want to buy other property by
selling your cars, her
husband is still in the car, then how do you transfer it
online Vinayak, after this day the
insurance of the town that has gone gets
transferred online, for that I need the
new RC which is
not shown in the name of the person who has taken the car of our husband, that is,
she will take an airport
commando proposal form, proposal for boys, you will get it from
where we will start it here
and you will have to
keep your password, so after opening, first of all
search Google Chrome app SBI General
Insurance, do that, like the person who has to
reduce the
general insurance, just
open it,
what happened, it was
looted, from where you have to do the
endorsement of your cars, bikes, that is, if you want to
change the owner, then you will see the crowd here, you have to
click on * and
for such issue, then you have to click here
Quick assist will be visible on it, click on it, like the
music has been downloaded,
change the claim status, do
not forget to transfer and share it online and
transfer of ownership, like I was holding it,
you have to tell this, you have to
enter the policy number of your vehicle or bike near it,
you will enter the registration number here,
MP3
and after that I will enter this number or engine
number, now the last five digits
and after that I have to fill this, you have to
call the plus minus one, click on next, as if
I can show you in
whose name any policy is and which
policy is it, one opinion Pankaj Bhai, which is it and
private motor 2314, enter it in family,
mobile number and email ID, not German
radio commentary box and there will be a
copy of updated RC and four teaspoon parties,
or you have to enter the one for drinking your lover,
in this you have to enter this 29 form which
accepts you till transfer only, after that there is a
photo ID proof option, like if you
accept your photo ID proof, Aadhar card,
voter card, then this idea is
not padal, NOC from old  And the sale deed
gives a letter to the person who is going to kill, that attitude
of the sale, you have to note it here and
you have to click on the proposal form here, if you want to
call the customer,
please show your settings, if you click on upload proposal form sign
and field by the knowledge, then
your form will be downloaded here, so
I have done all the forms etc., so
now I enter the mobile number,
email ID and if I click on the browser here, then
my phone number will be
uploaded here, I enter the details,
so friends, I have entered the details and while
uploading all the details here, it will be
trained here and your details will be
uploaded on the site, after that I do
submit, as soon as we submit,
this is the request to play skin tips, our
customer care team will get in touch with
you for any certificate, that
request will be generated here, if anyone wants to
paste them, you will get a call
and a link will appear on the Gmail ID which I have entered from
there  You can pay
like you can make green payment,
your polyp disease will come on mail and it can be
downloaded from here also, so friends,
we can do it like this, not with our ICICI
sorry license but with SBI endorsement, so
thank you friends.